dolphin.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy - Dolphin Browser for Android, iOS. Free

### Privacy

**Please click[here](http://dolphin-browser.com/privacy/privacy-policy-for-dolphin-browser/) to view Privacy Policy for Dolphin Browser.**

MoboTap Inc. (“MoboTap”) respects the privacy rights of our online visitors, and subscribers and members of our web site www.MoboTap.com (the “Site”) and is committed to protecting the personal information collected about you. To further this commitment, we have adopted this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to guide how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us. By visiting our Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

I. SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected online through the Site, and does not apply to information that may be collected by MoboTap offline. By using and submitting personal information, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. MoboTap reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Site. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. Your continued use of any of our websites will signify your acceptance of these changes

II. INFORMATION COLLECTED

Non-personally-identifying information MoboTap collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. MoboTap’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how MoboTap’s visitors use its website. From time to time, MoboTap may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. Personal Information To access certain services offered via the Site, MoboTap may collect information about you, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us. The types of personal information collected in conjunction with the activities listed above will vary depending on the activity. The requested information may include: (i) your name, (ii) mailing address, (iii) telephone number Use of Cookies MoboTap may use cookies on its Site. A “cookie” is a small bit of record-keeping information that sites often store on a user’s computer. Cookies do not include people’s names, email addresses, or other information that is personally identifiable; they are typically used to quickly identify a user’s computer and to “remember” things about the user’s visit. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.

III. USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

MoboTap may use your Personal Information to send you information about our company or our features, products or services, or promotional material from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary, unless the customer has disagreed that MoboTap uses its data. MoboTap also may use your Personal Information for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users’ behavior, for product development, for content improvement, and to customize content and layout of the Site. Names, postal and e-mail addresses and phone numbers collected may be added to our databases and used for business calls and mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events and the status of orders placed online. If you no longer wish to receive promotions or other offers, please click the unsubscribe button in our newsletter e-mail.  MoboTap does not sell or rent your Personal Information to third-parties for marketing purposes without your consent. MoboTap may share your Personal Information you provide with MoboTap subsidiaries and related companies. MoboTap may share Personal Information with business partners that assist MoboTap in providing you services. MoboTap is committed to giving you the choice whether or not MoboTap uses your information for marketing purposes or shares information with business partners.

IV. SAFEGUARDS

MoboTap maintains appropriate safeguards that ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of the personal information we collect. Personal information collected by MoboTap is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public and that are only accessible by authorized employees.

V. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

You should be aware that the Site may from time to time contain links to third-party web sites. MoboTap is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. If you are concerned about the privacy policy of a certain third party, we recommend that you read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any personal information.

VI. CONTACT US

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact our Privacy Policy Administrator through one of the following ways: Email: [legal@mobotap.com](mailto:legal@mobotap.com)
